Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Shit.
Hello?
NAOMI [over phone]:
Andy.
Yeah. Naomi?
W-Wait, where are you?
How come you're not home?
I'm-I'm sorry to wake you
in the middle of the night.
Hey, what's going on?
Where are you?
Listen, I'm gonna tell you,
but I don't want you
to freak out, okay?
Wait a minute, freak out?
What's going on?
You're scaring me.
Are you okay?
Yeah. No, I'm okay. Um...
I'm gonna be fine.
But, Andy...
I'm in rehab.
No, hon, seriously,
where are you?
-I'm in rehab.
- You're what?!
No... [stammers] That's
why I said don't freak out!
Okay? I checked myself in,
like, an hour ago.
Didn't you notice
I didn't come home?
Wait a minute. Hold on.
Wait.
Wait a minute.
What are you talking about?
Why would you...
Why would you be in rehab?
For what?
Because I need help,
Andy. Why else?
Wait a minute. What...
Wait a minute.
What are you talking-- I don't
understand. -Okay, hold on.
- Are you telling me--
- Help with what?
This is amazing.
- You didn't know?
- Know what?
- Oh, my God. Unbelievable.
-  Naomi, I don't know--
- Unbelievable.
- I-I-I don't--
Of course. -Thought you were
lying there in bed with me.
No, I don't know...
Honey. Honey, look.
Naomi, look,
sometimes you probably drink
a little too much.
- Oh, Andy, come on.
- It's not good, I know.
But, you know,
everybody does that.
- But rehab? You're crazy.
- No, it's not--
It-- Listen,
it is not the drinking.
I have to take something
to wake up. -What?
And I take something
to go to sleep.
And I... I've seen
every doctor in L.A.
I even had to drive
to Orange County.
Orange County? What the--
You... [stammers] -Yeah.
Wait a minute. This is, like...
Honestly, honestly, I'm
telling you, this is so insane.
I feel like I'm hallucinating
or something.
Of course you didn't know.
Why would you know?
You're out the door
every morning
before I can get a word in,
and you're out every night
for work.
We lead totally separate lives,
and I'm just...
- I'm invisible.
-  So this is my fault?
How can you know nothing
about my life?
I have this enormous weight,
and I've been carrying it
around for so long.
And I cannot do it anymore.
Wai-Wait a minute,
wait a minute.
Wait. Okay.
This is just not true.
- How can you say that?
- This is just not true.
Then enlighten me.
Okay. You're upset.
I get that.
But, h-honey, I know you.
You're a wonderful mother.
I'm sorry.
- The woman I live with...
- Andy.
...doesn't have
a drug addiction. -Andy.
- You just don't.
- Hey. Hey.
You're not hearing me.
You're not listening to me.
I've checked into
a rehabilitation center
- called Journeys.
- Journeys?
It's on Malibu Canyon Road.
It has yellow walls and a woman
at the front desk named Cecile,
and I am staying here
for 90 days. -
Wait a minute. What?
- I got to go.
- 90 days?
- Take care of the kids, Andy.
You'll do great.
Wait, no. No, no, no.
I'm coming up right now.
Just stay put, and we'll talk.
NAOMI [distorted]:
No, don't come...
Can't-- I can't hear you.
Wait, you're cutting out.
No, I said don't come, Andy.
Look, look, h-here, I'll be
up there in an hour. -No.
I'll be up there in an hour.
We'll drive back down here
and we'll talk about it.
Andy, do-do not come.
I am... you.
I c-- I can't hear you.
I'm leaving you.
What?
I'm leaving you!
-
...deep breaths,
in and out, in and out.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I'm late. -No, no,
it's okay. Don't worry.
Hi. -I wish we could
start without you. Hi.
- Mm.
- So how did it go?
I don't know
why this is still a thing.
I should not be this afraid
to tell my female boss
that I'm pregnant.
Uh, Grace,
this happens every day.
Come. Flip with me.
Okay.
- Okay.
- Hello, both of you!
Hi. -Dr. Verma,
I'm so sorry I'm late.
Oh, that is
totally, totally fine.
Okay.
How are you two doing?
Actually, I'm-I'm having
really bad heartburn.
- Oh, no.
- Here.
- Mm-hmm.
- Is that, um... is that normal?
- Uh...
- Well, we had Thai last night.
Couldn't that be why?
I think it could be why.
-I would just
avoid fried food or spicy food
- at this stage.
-Okay.
Well, let's just add that
to the list.
No spicy food, no fried food,
no caffeine, no alcohol,
- no sushi...
- No sex.
Actually, perfectly fine
to have sex.
Good, even.
I knew it. I'm-I'm a doctor,
for God's sake.
'Kay. -Mwah. I knew that
wasn't true. -
- Okay.
All right.
Just take a look, shall we?
Do you hear that sound?
It's the sound of
a perfectly healthy heartbeat.
- Just answer him.
- No, baby.
It's fine. It's okay.
Grace, my advice to
you, as always, is relax.
Everything looks fantastic.
And I will see you guys back
in a month.
-Great.
- Okay. Thank you.
-Of course.
-Oh, Dr. Verma,
- can I ask you a question?
- Yeah. Will you follow me?
- You good?
- Yeah. For sure.
What's up, Dad?
Naomi's in rehab.
What?
She's addicted to pills, apparently.
And-and-and she's left me.
We're separated, I guess.
Jesus.
Wait, seriously?
Yes. Seriously.
What about the twins?
Do they know?
I'll talk to them tonight.
- Dad.
- I will. I already told them
Naomi had a doctor's
appointment this morning.
You didn't seem really
surprised when I told you
Naomi's in rehab.
Did you suspect something
about her?
I don't know. I guess it's not,
like, that big of a shocker.
Not a shocker?
What's that mean?
Oh, look, uh,
let me-- let me... -Hey.
...let me call you back
from the car, okay? -Let's go.
- I-I got to go.
-Okay. But, wait,
did you know
she was taking pills?
Dad, I got to go.
I'll call you right back.
God, is there traffic
all the time? -
What is it? What's he want?
Well, so, Naomi checked herself
into rehab
and she left him.
Stop. What...
Wait, wait,
what's she in rehab for?
Prescription drugs, I think.
How did he not tell you
about this before?
'Cause he didn't know.
Who doesn't know that
their wife is addicted to drugs?
What the fuck?
This looks like a country club.
Jesus.
Hi. I'm Andy Goodrich,
and I'm here to see
Naomi Parsons.
She checked in last night.
Hello.
Oh. Hi.
- Sorry.
- That's okay.
All right,
let me check on that for you.
And Ms. Parsons
is expecting you?
Yeah. No.
I mean, not really.
But I'm her husband.
- So...
- Right.
Well, I am so sorry,
Mr. Goodrich.
We're not at liberty
to confirm or deny
that Ms. Parsons is here.
No, I know she's here.
I mean...
I mean, I know she's here
'cause she told me she's here.
I didn't know
that she was checking in,
- so yeah.
- And I understand that.
And I will let her know
that you've stopped in.
Well, no, just tell her
I'm here now.
I mean, you don't have to--
Here I am now. Just-just...
let her know. -I wish I could,
but I just can't.
Do you have, like,
some sort of a...
I don't know, say, somebody...
- a little higher up? Yeah.
- Oh. Yeah, sure.
And I'm afraid she's just
gonna tell you that Ms. Parsons
has pulled both her and
our consent to speak with you.
Okay.
Okay, look--
I can leave a message.
- I'll leave a message.
- Okay.
I want to see my fucking wife!
-I'm sorry.
- Hello?
-Hi.
I'm calling from Crosswinds
Park Elementary School.
- Yeah.
- Is somebody coming
to pick up Billie and Mose?
- BILLIE and MOSE: Dad.
- Sorry. I said I was sorry.
I mean, what do you want me
to say? -
I didn't realize
it was a half day,
and I was far away, so...
It's just so embarrassing
not getting picked up.
I mean, it's, like,
pretty much the worst feeling
- in the entire world.
- It's like the worst feeling
in the entire world
or it is the worst feeling
in the entire world? -Hey,
if you don't want me to talk
like I'm from L.A.,
don't raise me in L.A.
Hey, hey, hey, don't do that.
You're gonna scratch
the dining room table.
Come on.
Where's Mom?
She would never forget.
Yeah, and Mom always leaves
a glass of water
by my bed at night,
and she didn't last night.
Yeah.
I-I wanted to tell you guys
something about Mom, okay?
Uh...
What gives?
Mom had to go back home
for a little while
to see Grandma.
Mom's in St. Louis?
I thought you said she had
a doctor's appointment
this morning.
Yeah. No.
I'm sorry. I said that
because I didn't...
want you guys to worry.
But Mom had to go back and see
Grandma because, you know,
she's not feeling very well.
It's nothing serious,
but, you know, sh...
And, you know,
she's getting older,
so Mom wanted to go back and be
with her for a little bit.
Grandma's the same age as you.
No, she's not.
No, she's not. She... Sh...
Good deal older than I am.
But, anyway...
So, it's just gonna be us then?
Yeah.
Just us.
It's gonna be fun, right?
Be good.
Right?
I'm gonna go play Forza.
Hey, wait, I get to use
the computer first today!
Whoever gets to it first
gets to use it first.
You used it two days
over the weekend.
I did not...
Mom says
we're not supposed to have
this much gluten, you know.
She says it's bad for our guts.
Honey, honey, honey.
Put a paper towel down.
You have to respect wood.
It sounds like
Mom's maybe making you...
a little bit crazy.
Tell you why.
'Cause gluten happens to be...
delicious.
Mmm!
That's some good gluten.
Okay, want me
to make you a plate?
- Um, we do it ourselves.
- Okay.
Well, then bon appétit!
Dad, are there nuts in that?
- Why? Are you allergic?
- Mose is.
Mose. Oh, shit, I forgot.
Jesus, spit.
Spit, spit. Here, gimme.
- Mose. Give it to me.
- Oh, my God.
- Spit. Spit.
- Come on! Dad.
Jesus.
Pasta with butter and cheese.
- Specialty of the house.
- Mom puts salt in the water.
Good tip. That's a good tip.
Salt, salt, salt, salt.
I see pepper.
- I don't see--
- Top shelf.
Oh.
Kind of far for salt.
Here you go. Some salt.
Hey, Dad,
can we watch TV while we eat?
Can't we just talk?
I'm going out tonight, and...
and, uh...
I don't know.
Just rather spend time together
before I go out.
Where are you going?
- Got a thing.
- What kind of thing?
Dinner thing.
- We're eating dinner right now.
- I know.
But this is a dinner-work thing.
I'm gonna meet a new artist.
- Who's babysitting us?
- Tali.
Did you know
Tali was in the Israeli army?
That's why I hired her.
Did you know that
she smokes cigarettes outside?
That's new information.
Thank you.
I'm gonna talk to her
about that.
This about the smoking?
She's a narc, that little girl.
No, it's not about the smoking,
but, you know, if you could,
you know, maybe do a few less
cancer-causing habits
around the kids, that'd be
a good thing, okay? -
No, uh,
what I wanted to say is...
Naomi's gone away.
And, uh...
I'm gonna need an extra hand.
No problem.
Where she go? Rehab?
You knew about this?
Andy, of course I know.
Course I know. Good for her.
It's good. She's getting help.
Why are you stressed?
You didn't know?
- I didn't know.
- Ah.
Andy, this is not good.
I know. -Listen,
I'll help, okay? I understand.
- Marriage is tough, okay?
- Yeah, yeah.
My-my husband is a gay.
What do you mean
your husband is a gay?
Eh, my husband is gay.
He lives in Tel Aviv.
Very good-looking boyfriend.
I mean, uh, mamash wow!
Don't blame him.
Wait a minute, he's a gay?
He's got a--
he's got a boyfriend?
- Why are you still together?
- Why not?
Andy, loosen up.
What time you'll be home?
3:00, 4:00 in the morning?
No. Like, 11:00.
What do you mean,
3:00 in the morning? -Okay.
- Hey! Becca. You're back.
- Hey!
Yes. -How you doing?
How you feeling?
- So much better.
- Good, good.
- Thanks, Andy.
- I'm glad you're back.
Hey. Careful.
Don't drop that, boys.
Yeah.
Perfect.
- Good.
-Oh, good, you're here.
Finally.
The sign outside.
Yeah.
Killing me. Looks horrible.
Worse every day.
Get me a second quote
for a new one, okay?
8,000.
8,000?
- I'll-I'll get a third quote.
- Yeah.
- How did dinner go last night?
- I don't know.
Think he's talking to
a lot of people, which is,
you know, cool.
- Did he call?
- Uh, no.
But Dev did, and y-you're not
gonna like this,
but he decided to give the piece
that you wanted to sell to Inga
to his mother.
Get-- Are you serious?
God. You know what,
get him on the phone.
I'll-I'll talk-- No.
Get me the mother.
Okay. And just a reminder--
you have Back-to-School Night
tonight.
Naomi asked me to put it
on your schedule
- in case you can make it.
- Okay.
Do all the parents do that
or is that, like,
an optional thing?
I-I don't-- I don't know, man.
I'm 27.
Cy's in your office.
You guys had a meeting
with an accountant,
like, 15 minutes ago.
Yeah, yeah.
Andy, you asked for it
in black and white, so...
Look, I can't control
the market, right?
I mean, you know,
nobody needs a painting.
Let's rewind for a sec. So you
took a loan out from the bank
to meet your obligations,
but there are salaries
to pay here, Andy.
Too many
for what you're bringing in.
I've been telling you this
for months.
Yeah,
we've been discussing that.
Oh. -It's just... coming up
on the end of the year,
we're not sure
it's the best time
- to let people go.
- Right.
Guys, come on.
You're just covering costs.
And then each month, the tidal
wave rolls through again.
You have to borrow
from Peter to pay Paul.
At some point, Peter goes broke.
May I?
- Please.
- Andy.
I think, in fact, it may be
time to consider relocating.
I know we've been here 26 years,
but the rent is killing us.
Cy.
Come on.
There's history here, you know?
28 years, by the way.
Andy, look at it this way.
Your artists just aren't
commanding the prices
that the real estate demands.
Right?
Last month, I suggested selling
inventory at a reduced rate.
And we tried that, but...
He's right. We tried it.
I can't reduce any more.
I'll lose all my artists.
- Can't do it.
- Uh-huh.
Got this young guy right now.
I'm telling you, there's heat--
am I right, Cy?-- all around
this kid. -Yeah. -Oh.
Dev's great. People love him.
Really good.
Has he sold yet? No.
I-Is that whose work
is out there now?
Yeah.
Oh. Yeah.
Look, here's the thing--
you guys...
you guys are in debt.
And at some point,
the faucet gets turned off.
Look, we've been having
these meetings once a month
for, what, seven months,
and there's been no improvement.
In fact,
things have gotten worse.
I'd say, without a new show--
and a fruitful one--
you are looking at, I don't--
like, a few more months.
Tops.
I'm sorry.
When we first moved in,
it was us,
a tattoo parlor and a toy store.
Now it's just, you know,
sneaker shops,
and half the block
is an Apple Store.
MALE VOICE [over phone]: All of
our agents are currently busy
assisting other callers.
Press one to have an agent
call you back. -Representative.
Sorry, I didn't catch that.
Would you like an agent
to call you back?
God, this thing is defective!
Sorry, I didn't catch that.
Would you like an agent to
call you back? -Representative!
- Sorry, I didn't catch that.
-  -
Sorry, I didn't catch that.
Dad, I can't talk right now.
I've been on the line
with the delivery service
delivering my changing table
for 45 minutes.
I have to call you back.
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait.
Just give me a second.
Honey, hey,
I really need your help
tonight, pal.
I'm in a bind here.
There's a thing at school.
Uh, it slipped my mind.
Tali can't stay, and I need
somebody to watch the kids.
Could you watch the kids for me
tonight, please?
Gracie, come on.
- What do you say?
- No.
No. I'm sorry. No.
- Really?
- Yeah. Really.
Why not?
Because I, you know,
have, like...
a million things going on.
I don't know. I-I have work
and I'm pregnant and...
Okay.
I-I don't want to.
Wait. Look,
I really need your help, babe.
Really, honestly.
I mean, I-I never ask you
for your help, do I? I don't.
I mean, I'm under
such stressful-- Oh, God.
You have no idea how stressful
the circumstances are right now.
Honestly. So I just need you--
It'll be for a couple of hours.
That's it--
couple of hours, okay?
This is me begging you.
I'm begging now, okay?
I'm begging you,
my daughter, for help.
'Kay?
How often do I ever do this?
Like, when do I do this?
Do you really want me
to answer that?
Lately. Lately.
I was just gonna say "lately."
I was just gonna say it.
I was gonna say,
"When-when-when d--
lately I asked you... honey?"
How long are you pregnant for?
Nine months.
Ten, technically.
And how much longer
until you're finished?
Three and a half more months.
Do you know if it's
a boy or a girl? -No.
- We want to be surprised.
- Why?
Pete does.
Actually, I really want to know.
What do you hope it is?
A girl, obviously.
Sorry.
I get it.
Right.
Are you excited to be a mom
or not really?
Yes.
Okay, so, uh, you guys...
must be hungry.
Uh, let's see,
what's your dad got here?
I bet he's got, like,
pasta with butter and cheese.
Why do you always say
"your dad"?
Isn't he all of our dads?
Well, I'm 27 years older
than you,
which is basically unheard of
for siblings.
Except maybe in L.A.
Wait, you're 36?
Is your mom good at math?
'Cause you definitely
didn't inherit
that skill from my father.
Our father.
Oh, right. Okay.
Hey.
Oh.
Hi, Daddy. Oh.
I don't-- I don't know
why I just called you that.
Hey, Dad. Wha-What-What are
you doing home so early?
What's up? -Uh, you know me.
I ducked out early.
- Look at you. How you doing?
- Hi.
- Good.
- Man, oh, man, oh, man.
Get bigger every day.
You look fantastic, kiddo.
Really. Look so good.
- Hope it's a girl.
- Dad.
I do.
Sorry. It'd be great.
Can't believe
my baby's having a baby.
- Yeah.
- You hungry?
I'm starved.
Do I have any food?
So, you go
to things like this now?
Parent/teacher conferences?
Yeah.
What are you talking about?
I did all that stuff with you.
- Never.
- Oh, come on.
Geez, Grace, give me a break.
What do you want from me?
I did my best.
Do we not have
a good relationship?
We do.
It's just that when I was
Billie and Mose's age,
I hardly saw you.
There were trips to London
and Switzerland,
Miami, New York.
I mean...
you practically lived
at the gallery.
I mean, it's okay, but let's
be honest-- I was there, too.
We went to New York together,
you and I, remember?
Once. We went once.
Yeah! Remember,
we had such a nice time?
We went to see,
uh, uh, the Rockettes.
I took you to Serendipity.
Am I not the president
of your fan club?
I am.
That piece you wrote about
the death of arthouse theaters,
that was great writing.
I showed it
to everybody in the office.
They loved it.
Did Cy email you?
Yes, yes, he did.
You know what,
this conversation's
really stressing me out.
I got, I got work I have to do.
I have to clean out
the coat closet
to make room
for all the baby stuff.
My back hurts like hell.
And I have a human head
wedged between my ribs.
So if you'll excuse me.
- Ah.
- You know what?
You must really love what you do
to be away
from your kids to do it,
because I'm already wondering,
do I really care
about the dumb shit
that I write about?
And I haven't even met
my kid yet.
I might not even like them.
What do you mean, dumb shit?
You don't write dumb shit.
You're a great writer.
What are you talking about?
Why? Are you thinking
about quitting?
You're the senior
entertainment writer.
I know my title, Dad, thank you.
You know,
forget I said anything.
And... you're welcome
for watching your kids.
Where are you going?
Have some pi--
I was just gonna say thank you.
If you gave me a chance,
I was just about
to say thank you.
What,
does Pete want you to quit?
You know,
what is your deal with Pete?
Huh? He's a fantastic person.
He's next-level reliable,
he's sweet,
he's a brilliant doctor.
He's not the type of guy
that would ever,
ever ask me to quit my job.
- I...
- What?
- What? What?
- Nothing.
I mean, I-- I mean...
To be honest, he's an ear,
nose and throat doctor.
- But that's okay. I mean, not--
-  Oh, my God.
So an ear, nose
and throat doctor isn't
a cool enough job for you,
huh, Mr. Cool Guy?
No, no, no, look, I do.
I like him very much, I do.
I really like him.
I do.
He's, he's a nerd,
and that's okay, it's...
- Some people are nerds.
- Okay, you know what?
No, I'm not gonna
get stressed out.
It's not healthy, and I'm
already way too stressed out!
Okay, okay.
Now, don't get so stressed.
Just relax. We're just talking.
You know what, you...
you have a complex
about traditional things.
It's not a direct offense to you
that I don't follow
your La bohème school
of living life in reverse.
I want order.
I wanted to get married
and start a family
and, I don't know!
Okay, maybe, maybe
I'm just future tripping here
and thinking that I don't want
to leave my baby
to go write profile pieces
on some TikTokers.
Okay, you're not making
any sense right now.
Because first you said
you don't even know
if you're gonna like the kid,
and now you're
quitting your job just
to spend more time with them.
- So it's-it's--
-  I'm processing.
- Okay.
- This is my process.
- I get it, I get it, okay.
- I'm just processing.
Wait, I get it now, okay,
just don't get stressed.
What do you want me to do
to help? -Just help!
Dad, don't ask, just do.
Okay, I'm-I'm just better
when I'm told how to help.
I'm just...
Oh, my God, I wish I could
record this conversation
and play it back
for my therapist.
See, does Pete know
how funny you are?
- Yes, he does.
- Okay.
- Do you want to really help?
- Yes.
Okay, come shopping with me
for some baby stuff.
Pete's on call all week.
And-and-and the stores are
crowded on the weekends.
And I just don't have
the patience to go by myself.
Done. Done. Set. Play--
It's, it's kind of far away.
No, I want to go, I-- Honey?
I love hanging out with you,
so I'm good.
Let's go. I'll just go
no matter how far it is.
- Any day next week.
- Okay.
Tuesday, can't.
And, uh, I'm not sure
about Thursday, but just...
Just-just email me your
availability, okay? -Okay.
- Okay, good, can't wait.
- Okay.
- Love you.
- Okay, great.
You've never looked better ever.
-Hey, Dad?
-Hmm?
Did you see our self-portraits
in the art room at school?
I did.
I thought they were
fantastic, really.
Your use of sunlight
is, ooh, so sweet.
And, Mose,
you've got this kind of
Basquiat-ish vibe going,
which I'm totally digging.
Very abstract. Very good.
Very, very good.
Hold on, I got to get this.
Hey. What'd you think?
Tell me that piece is not you.
Huh? Really?
-Dad?
- Really?
Me, I think it's stunning.
Dad, what's "rehab"?
Gonna m--
H-Hold on a minute.
Yeah, ring you back.
Bye. Excuse me?
A girl at school said
that her mom said that
that's where our mom is.
Is that true?
No, it's not true.
It's absolutely not true.
Who told you that? What girl?
I'm gonna call her mother.
I'm just gonna Google it
if you don't tell me.
Okay.
Okay, look.
Rehab is a place where people go
who aren't feeling well.
They go there
to get to feel better.
But that's not
where your mom is.
Mom's in St. Louis.
She told us yesterday.
When did you talk
to your mother?
She calls us after school.
Why is that weird?
It's not weird. It's not weird.
It's not weird at all.
It's good.
Come on, come on, shortstop.
Grab your, uh,
grab your backpack.
We got to get going.
What are you gonna be
for Halloween this year, Mose?
-The alien/car from Forza.
-What?
That doesn't even make sense.
Dad, can we go
Halloween shopping soon?
Halloween?
It was just summer.
- Holy mackerel.
- Come on.
We're gonna be late for school.
- Okay.
- Our school is
- really strict about tardiness.
- Okay, okay, okay.
Okay, let's go.
Hi, Cy. It's Billie.
Can he call you back?
We're late for school.
How'd you get my phone?
Hey, ask him if he saw
the article in the Times.
- Did you see the... He saw.
- Okay.
Hey, tell him to have Jonny
get a number on the daughter.
Can you have Jonny get
a number on the daughter?
Name?
- Lola, Lola Thompson.
All right, he'll be in
in an hour. Bye.
- Okay, let's go.
- Where are our lunches?
You can't get them at school?
I pay all this money
for the school
and they don't feed you?
If you ever took us to school,
you'd know that
they only give us lunches
on very special days
like Taco Tuesdays.
And today is not
one of those days.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, come on.
Just get in the car. Let's go.
We'll pick something up
on the way.
Hey, come on. Hey.
Sorry we're late. We're...
Oh. Sorry. 'Scuse me.
All right. -Bye. -Bye. See you.
Yeah, hey, hi.
We're late a little bit. -Hi.
Um, these are my kids.
- They're in, uh, third grade.
- Fourth grade.
They're in, uh, fo--
Uh, they're in, uh...
What's your teacher's name?
The one with the hair?
Uh, Miss G, you mean? -Yeah,
they're in Miss G's class.
Um, do you have a doctor's note?
Uh, yeah, no, we're-we're just,
you know,
good old-fashioned late.
I'm gonna have to mark them
both as tardy then.
- Dad! -
-No, no, this is my fault.
This is on me.
This is my fault.
I was reading a thing
in the paper.
I forgot about the lunches.
And, uh, next thing you know,
boom, it's 8:00.
So...
I'm sorry.
That's not how this works.
Tardy.
No.
It's 8:07.
That's not-- That's really not
even late, seven minutes.
Come on, you've never been late
for a lunch
or something like that?
- It's not a big deal. Just...
- Hi, hi, hi!
- Sorry we're late!
- Hey! Oh, not a problem, Terry.
Welcome, Alexander.
- Hey, Alex.
-  Okay, come here.
Come here, buddy.
Okay. Sorry, buddy.
- I'm so sorry.
- What's with this guy?
Alex is epileptic.
He's always at the doctor.
Ah.
I love you so much.
- Hey.
- Hey. How you doing?
- Oh, hey. Hi. How are you?
- Hey.
Boy, they are strict
around here, aren't they?
Yeah, they're pretty cool
with us,
but they can be kind of nuts
about tardiness. -Yeah.
I'm Terry, by the way.
Alexander's in class
- with Billie and Mose.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- I know. Yeah. Hi. Andy.
- Yeah. Yeah, I, uh,
saw you briefly
at the Back-to-School Night
- but didn't get a chance to...
- Yeah.
Hey.
If I'm out-of-bounds here,
tell me, but...
uh, Billie told me about
your little guy, Alexander.
Mm. -And, uh, sorry to hear.
That-That's rough, man.
- Oh.
- I've got...
Oh, geez. I'm sorry.
No, it's okay. I'm-I'm...
I'm fine.
- I'm so sorry.
- No, I'm fine.
Hold on a minute.
Hold on a minute. -I'm okay.
Here. Here. -Everything sets
me off. I'm an actor, so, uh...
- Oh. Yeah. It's clean.
- Oh. Thank you. That's-that's...
Thank you. I'm an actor,
so all my emotions
- are, like, right here.
- Oh, sure. Yeah.
What kind of stuff do you do?
Little bit of everything.
Mostly graphic design.
- Yeah. You know. Yeah.
- Sure. It's hard.
Yeah, I do graphic design
when I'm not shooting something,
and... lately,
I'm never shooting anything.
Oh, geez. Oh, man.
There I go again. -No.
This is so embarrassing.
-No. No.
- Look at that.
- Oh, wow.
- Two of 'em, right there.
- Very good.
- Once again, clean.
- Thank you.
I've just-- I've been off
since my husband left us.
I'm sorry to hear that.
That's... -Thank you.
How long has that been?
Three years.
- Three? Ah.
- Yeah.
And he's only seen Alex one time
- since he left.
- In three years?
Yeah. Can you believe that?
That's-- Sorry,
I don't know the guy,
but that's kind of schmucky.
Yes. Thank you.
It is schmucky.
- Yeah.
- Yeah. It was all just
"too much" for him.
But Alex and I are good.
We're in a total groove
with everything.
We got him
on the right medication.
His doctor is A-plus-plus.
- Oh, good.
- But, um...
Yeah, but then someone asks you
how your day's going
and suddenly you're crying
at drop-off. -Yeah.
Well...
Uh...
I'm actually...
kind of in the same boat.
Little bit.
- Oh.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Naomi and I are... Oh, yeah.
- Shut up.
Yeah. -Ah. That's why
she missed Back-to-School Night?
Well, sort of.
She-She's, uh...
seeing somebody.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
- Professional help.
- Oh.
There's a little bit
of a drug thing.
- Drug issue. Ish.
- Oh.
You know, she...
- she was doing drugs, so...
- Coke.
- No, no, no.
- Oh.
No.
No. Prescription pills.
Oh.
I'm the husband.
I don't even know about it.
- Right?
- Well...
No, no. I mean,
what's that say about me?
I don't-- Is this too much?
- 'Cause I'm... Should I...
- No. Oh, God, no.
- Seriously, though.
- No, come on.
I'm the guy--
I'm supposed to know--
I mean, tell me, am I in denial?
Am I just dumb? I don't know.
Yeah, yeah. Want to sit?
Let's sit. Absolutely.
Maybe she just needed a break
from it all, you know?
From me. You know?
You should see
the rehab center, by the way.
It's like the Four Seasons.
Who do you think's
paying for that?
-Well, she's taking
the steps towards recovery.
That's... that's good, right?
Families overcome these things.
Yeah, I know.
But she didn't clue me in.
I had no idea.
She didn't let me know
what she was going through,
and now I'm the bad guy.
I got to tell you something--
you're real easy to talk to.
Has anybody ever told you that?
Thanks. That's, um...
How-how does she sound
when you talk to her?
Every time I call, they won't
let me-- I can't see her.
They won't let me talk to her.
I'm completely in the dark.
Mm.
My advice,
you know, keep trying.
- Yeah.
- Keep calling.
I got to go. Um...
- Good luck.
- Oh. Thanks. Yeah.
- Take care, Andy.
- Yeah, sure.
- You got this, mama.
- Okay.
- Thanks.
-  All right.
I'm sorry for not being there
for you more.
I'm sorry, okay?
I just want to say
I hope you're getting
the help you need.
I'll be here for you.
And I miss you.
Hello?
Naomi?
Hello? Naomi.
Okay. Okay.
I-I know it's you.
Uh...
The kids told me...
you call 'em after school,
so I came home to talk to you.
Okay.
I can tell
you're not gonna say anything.
That-That's okay.
I'll-I'll do all the talking.
Okay?
Okay. I came to see you.
I'm sure... sure you know that.
And I've called every day
and left messages.
I don't know...
if you've gotten them or not.
Actually,
pretty sure you have, but...
I just wanted
to say some things, okay?
I want to say...
I'm sorry for not being there
for you more,
for not even knowing
to be there for you more.
I know things have been weird
between us recently,
and things have just... been off
and I... I ignored it.
I've been wrapped up
in the gallery
and all the stuff
that's going on there,
which is only getting worse,
by the way.
And I've been...
I've been in my own universe.
I know I have.
And I'm sorry. I apologize.
I hope you're getting
the help that you need.
And I'm here
whenever you're ready.
I'll just be here.
Okay? I'll be here for you.
The kids miss you like crazy.
And I miss you.
Naomi.
Okay, I get it. I get it.
You're not...
you're not gonna--
you're not gonna say anything.
That's okay.
So you can...
you can call back for the kids,
and, uh...
I-I won't answer.
I promise I won't pick up, okay?
O-Okay. Okay.
I love you.
Okay.
Okay, can you just explain
why you're not speaking with me?
MOSE [laughs]: Oh, my God.
Okay, okay, okay. Watch this.
Hey, guys,
where are you? I'm leaving.
But you need
to press that button on top.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
-I know.
- Not inside. Not inside.
- I'm pressing it.
Now make it go, like,
around the lamp.
- Make it come down. Come on.
-Okay. Watch.
Okay, okay.
Let's go.
Who got you that thing anyway?
You and Mom did.
Last Christmas.
- Ooh.
-Billie.
- Come on, come on.
- Oh, my God! -Relax.
Bring it down.
Give me the remote.
- We're having fun.
- I've got to go.
Billie! Hand me the remote!
-  You made me do that.
- Billie!
What is wrong with you?
What did I just say?
Do you know how valuable
that was? -It doesn't matter.
We're not even allowed to touch
anything in this house anyway.
Yes, you are.
You're just not allowed to fly
a fucking drone in my house.
You finally said it.
Your house.
It's your house!
I want Mom.
She likes us more than you do.
Really?
Well, Mom's not here, is she?
Billie, I'm sorry.
I-I'm sorry I raised my voice
and I used the f-word.
I was frustrated.
I yelled.
I shouldn't have done it.
Will you accept my apology, please?
Come on, honey.
I have to leave soon.
Hey, Tali, do you think
you can get the door?
What does it look like
I'm doing?
Bill, the food's here.
- Please. Honey.
- Just go!
You go out every night!
I have to go to work!
Somebody has to support the...
generations of children
who hate me.
Bill, please.
Hey.
How 'bout if I stay in tonight?
We can watch a movie together.
How's that sound?
So great.
I can't believe
you guys have never seen this.
Where would we have seen it?
RICK [on screen]:
My letter of transit?
I could use a trip.
It doesn't make
any difference about our bet.
You still owe me 10,000 francs.
And that 10,000 francs
should pay our expenses.
Our expenses?
-Mm-hmm.
-Louis,
I think this is the beginning
of a beautiful friendship.
Come on. It's perfect.
So, what'd you think?
I mean, they didn't even
end up together.
That's just, like... crazy.
I-I know.
That's what makes it a,
you know, really good
love story, though, you know?
It's kind of, uh...
what they call "bittersweet,"
you know?
Hey, look...
relationships aren't easy, pal.
How do you deal with having
so many girls in your life?
Not very well, my friend.
Not very well.
It's past your bedtime.
Let's go.
- D-Dad?
- Yeah?
Is Mom ever coming back?
Of course she is.
Of course she's coming back.
Why would you ask me that?
Just a feeling, I guess.
Hey, man, your mom loves you
way, way, way too much
not to come back.
Um... We're doing all right,
though, right?
Yeah.
We're doing pretty good.
All right.
Help me load up, uh,
the belle of the ball.
Okay.
Dad, will you close that
behind you?
- Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
- Thank you. Oof.
Here, let me get that.
Let me get those--
Dad, I'm fine.
I'm fine, I'm fine.
- All right.
-  Oh.
Hey, do you have any food?
Like, any hummus or anything?
What? What are you--
Hello?
- What's up?
- Hey, it's me and Jonny,
and we have some good news
and some bad news.
Okay, give me the, uh...
- give me the good news.
-Okay.
No, give me the bad news, right?
- All right, okay.
- Never mind.
- Just give me the good news.
- Well, so...
- Yeah. Go ahead.
- All right.
- Okay. So the good...
- Hey, hold-hold on a second.
- Bill, give me a second.
- Grace.
- What'd I say?
- Bill.
- Sorry.
- So many kids.
Who can keep track? -I know.
I'll-- Hold, hold on a second.
Hey. Hey. Hold on. Hold on.
- Yeah. Okay, go ahead.
-Okay. Okay.
Well, the good news is that
Theresa Thompson's daughter
isn't meeting with anybody
and she's not taking any calls.
That's good news?
She's performing tonight
in Hollywood. She's a singer.
We think you should go
down there and talk to her
and see what you can do.
Just show up? I mean--
What kind of singer is she?
Uh... well, it's...
looks like it's
some kind of a jazz club.
Oh. Cool.
Yeah, I can do that.
That'd be fun.
Uh...
Okay, what's the bad news?
I spoke with Dev earlier,
and, uh...
he's leaving us, Andy.
I'm so sorry.
I-I didn't expect that.
What did he say, exactly?
Why didn't he call me?
Well, he's nervous. He's young.
First shows
are always tough, Cy.
We've been through this
a million times.
We work hard for that kid,
and then he just
leaves us like that?
Did you tell him about the ad
we took out in the L.A. Times?
I told him about it.
But who's he gonna blame for
the work not selling? Himself?
Look, go down
to this jazz thing,
talk to Lola Thompson.
I know you.
And I know
you can make this happen.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Absolutely nothing.
I have to go
to this thing tonight.
Jazz club.
Check out this singer.
- It's for work.
- Mm-hmm.
Supposed to be
a very hip little club.
You want to come with me?
Your place looks fantastic,
by the way.
These chairs, are they new?
Nope. I've had them
for about a year.
- Really?
- Just, uh, you never come over.
Stop it.
I come over all the time.
- Yeah, okay.
- I do.
What do you say? You and me,
we'll go out
on the town tonight.
You and me, doing the town.
- Mm.
- Starts at 10:00. It'll be fun.
There's supposed to be
some good sushi over there.
10:00's a little rough
for me lately, Dad.
- Right.
- Yeah.
- Sorry. You're right.
Well, what are you
gonna do for dinner?
- Why don't you--
- Hello, mi familia.
Hey, Pete. So how you doing?
- Hey, Andy.
- Hi, bub.
Thank you so much
for taking her shopping.
I'm thrilled
I didn't have to go.
- Sure.
-Uh, really?
Yeah. I'm just saying.
You look very beautiful,
by the way. -Me?
-Uh-huh.
-You're crazy.
I am not.
Also, I picked up
from that Greek place you like.
Yeah?
- And the good froyo.
- Oh!
Yum.
Andy, I wish I knew
you were still here.
I would've gotten more kebabs.
No, I'm good. I'm--
I'll grab something to eat
on the way.
Uh, hey. This was fun today.
Wait-- No. Um...
- Here, I got it.
- No, stay.
Hold on.
Uh, Dad, why don't you stay?
We can-- we can
figure this out. -Yeah.
- There's enough food.
- Nah. Nah. I'll be good.
I'm good. Really.
Okay. Um...
Well... have fun.
Don't worry about me.
I'm good. Thanks, kiddo.
- See ya.
- Later, Pete.
- Hey.
- Oh, hi.
- Ticket booth's over there.
- Okey doke.
- Thanks.
- Mm-hmm.
- Hi.
How are you? Hey, is this
the, uh, Lola Thompson show?
Uh...
Wait. Are you...
Lola...
Is-- Are you with her, or...
No, she's... Is she perform--
She's supposed
to be performing. -Wait.
Uh, yeah. Probably.
Uh, I think.
Yeah, actually, Lola Thompson,
- yes, she's right there.
- There it is.
Oh, good, good. Now what?
- I mean, do we, uh...
- Oh, it's $20.
- There you go. There you go.
- Yeah.
But 25 if online.
No. I... we're...
Here we are, paying now.
And it's
"a night of feminist works."
Enjoy.
Oh.
Yay, women supporting women.
I've had an amazing time.
I feel like
our periods are gonna be
all synced up after tonight.
Thank you so much.
I'm out of here, guys.
You guys are fantastic.
Enjoy the rest of your night.
I should stop being desperate.
-Let's give it up
for Lola Thompson!
♪ Love ♪
♪ I want to make love
to your existence ♪
♪ Drenched in the colors
of your energy ♪
♪ Then masturbate
to the memories ♪
♪ I want to lose myself
inside yourself ♪
♪ Until you find me,
confine me ♪
♪ To the freedom
of your prisons ♪
♪ Exist in the same place,
same time ♪
♪ Combine until your thoughts
slow-grind with mine ♪
♪ Combine until your
thoughts slow-burn with mine ♪
♪ Combine until your thoughts
slow-grind with mine ♪
♪ My, I want to drink
the sweat of your intellect ♪
♪ Reflect and watch
the night passion mark my neck ♪
♪ I want to make love
to my soulmate ♪
♪ Oh, shit... ♪
LOLA [singsongy]:
Somebody gave me flowers.
-  This is...
-Uh, excuse me. Uh, Lola?
Hi.
- Hey.
- Hey. Uh... First of all,
that was
a really interesting show.
I wasn't, you know,
ready for that.
- But it was great.
- Thank you.
- Andy Goodrich.
- Nice to meet you, Andy.
- Yeah.
I was hoping we could...
chat for a little bit.
Well, I was on my way out, so...
I own the Goodrich Gallery,
here in L.A.
Oh. Okay. Yeah.
I was wondering if we could
talk about your mother Theresa.
Your-- your mother,
comma, Theresa,
- not Mother Teresa.
- I got you. Um...
I'm so sorry,
but I'm not really talking
to people just yet.
- Yeah.
- You know? I need...
just a little while
to think things through.
She just passed.
Yeah, no, I get it.
Totally understand, really.
I just want to tell you
I am such a fan
of your mom's work,
like, for decades,
and she wasn't discovered till,
you know,
really late in her career.
Yeah, well, she was lucky.
She always said,
"If you're a female artist,
- you're bound..."
-"Bound to be dead
before you make any money."
Yeah, I know.
She said that to me, too.
Hmm.
You know,
I remember the first time
I came across
your mother's work.
I immediately bought
this really nice little piece,
and I really wanted
to represent her,
but, you know,
she had already gone elsewhere.
I'm telling you,
here's what I think we do:
we-we raise her visibility,
you know,
which in turn's gonna
raise her price,
but she deserves it,
I'm telling you--
Sorry.
My mind is going
a million miles an hour.
I'm so excited
talking about this. -Okay.
How do I know you're not gonna
just tag her into a show
with other Black female artists?
Solo presentation only. Look.
I know we're only
a little boutique gallery,
but that's to your advantage.
You're gonna get approached
by everyone,
if you haven't already.
Have you already?
Uh... no one else was
the only man at my show tonight.
I go to every feminist works
night I can get to.
Okay.
Last thing
before I cut you loose.
Everywhere else,
you're just gonna be one of,
you know,
ten or 20 different estates.
You're just gonna be
on the director's to-do list.
If you come with me, you get me.
Okay, this has been
the longest day,
and right now my mind is just
on a hot shower, so...
- I will come to your gallery.
- Cool.
And we will meet more formally.
That is more than
I've offered anyone.
Cool.
And yes, there are others.
How many others? I'm joking.
Okay, Halloween costumes!
Let's do this.
Okay, you guys know
what you want?
Can we divide and conquer?
-Ah!
- Nice, nice.
- Wow.
Anyway, what was I saying?
- You're a loser.
- Yes.
Eh... not my words, yours.
- And you're not.
- Right.
Well, I'm told
time heals all wounds, but...
I'm just sitting here, waiting,
and no healing.
You know?
You just got
to get out there, man.
Get out in the world more.
Look at you.
Really nice guy,
good-looking dude,
great dad.
Just gotta power through
this thing, man.
- Come on.
- Thanks, Andy.
How about you? How's
your healing process going?
Not good.
Still haven't heard from Naomi.
I don't know. Hate it.
I was over at my daughter
and her husband's house
the other day.
You know, it was--
I don't know, it was odd.
It made me feel like, uh...
...lonely, actually.
Yeah.
- Yeah, lonely.
-Dad! Dad, Dad!
Look at this Boba Fett costume!
Cool!
There's a jet pack
and arm guards
and an ammunition belt!
Aw. Man, this is
really, really great.
You know what, bud?
It's a little pricy.
I bet we could find something
even cooler than this.
Oh. Okay.
Ooh, I don't think so.
Love it. I love it.
Good find, dude.
Excellent find.
Stick it in the bag.
-Yes.
- That's going with us. -Ah. No.
Andy, you don't have to
do that. -No, it's on me.
- No...
- Forget about it, man.
- Don't worry about it.
- We'll get something else.
- He'll wear it one time.
- It's so not a big deal.
Don't...
Thank you. That's so nice.
Have you thought about
telling the kids
the truth about Naomi?
I mean, I'm sure
they already have a hunch.
They're so intuitive, you know?
They-they know so little,
but they pick up on so much.
- They're funny like that.
- I-I have.
It just... seems like the end
of something for them, I think.
You know? I mean, they still
believe in the Tooth Fairy.
They don't even like it
when their meat touches
their vegetables on their plate.
- Dad, Dad, Dad, Dad, Dad!
-Hey, hey, hey, hey!
- What do we got? What do we got?
- Uh-oh. Uh-oh.
'Cause I got about five minutes
of this place left in me.
Okay. I'm going to be
a demented zombie,
and Mose is gonna be
a dead alien ghost.
It's gonna be so awesome.
Okay. Okay.
I think I have a better idea.
Trick or treat!
WOMAN [laughs]:
Wow, what do we have here?
A hip old man
and a beautiful young señorita.
Oh, look! Boba Fett!
Okay. Give it back.
Okay, wait. Okay,
I'll trade you for this candy.
Hey. Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa. Let me look here.
Dad, I already checked.
No nuts.
- Thank you.
- Let me double-check.
I'll give you this one.
- Boo!
-  Oh, my God.
Andy, you scared me.
This house is incredible.
Yeah. Thanks.
- It's a nice house.
- It's so nice
and cozy and chic and...
- Yeah.
- ...like, perfect.
How long have you lived here?
Since, uh, 17? No, 18 years.
- Oh, wow.
- Yeah. 18 years.
Hey, you drink whiskey?
Uh, you know, I'm more of
a rosé fella, but yeah, sure.
- Thank you.
-  There you go.
Yeah. I bought it right after
my, uh, divorce from Ann.
Oh, Ann.
That's your
older daughter's mom, right?
- Yeah. Right.
- How long were you two married?
Uh, 14 years.
- Hmm.
- She's in the art world, too.
Hmm. -She's, uh, the director
of the Walton Museum downtown.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
Museum director.
That's a big job.
Yeah, it is.
Actually really knows
the art world.
She's pretty brilliant,
I gotta say.
Which, uh, explains...
...probably why
she left me, but...
You know,
this is actually really good.
Yeah, it should be.
- 31-year-old bottle there, pal.
- What?
Andy, are you nuts?
Don't waste this on me.
I wouldn't even know
the difference.
Sure you would.
You're a man of taste, I think.
And seem to be a guy who enjoys
the finer things in life.
Anyway, just enjoy it.
How often do I get to, you know,
drink with an elf?
Mm.
- Okay, wow.
- Is that a good okay?
Good okay? Bad okay?
- Good, good...?
- Well...
Fuck!
Oh, fuck!
Oh... Oh...
Let me start by saying sorry.
-  Oh, my God.
- Dude. So not a big deal.
You know, I just-- I've been
out of the game so long.
Sure! -And I-I thought
the roaring fire
and the sexy music
and the 30-year-old whiskey...
I just, I don't--
I-I thought things were
getting romantic? -Right.
So, I could see a guy go,
"Yeah, he's..." but...
By the way, let me ask--
Do I seem gay, though?
Do I? -I am
very uncomfortable right now.
- No, dude. I'm telling you--
- Anyway, um...
Great seeing you, man.
Alex! Let's go!
You know what?
For the record,
I'm way too young for you.
Well, that's hardly
the issue here, pal.
You told me to get out there.
Meet new people.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
but I didn't mean me.
I wasn't talking about me.
It was that 30-year-old whiskey.
Shame on you for serving me
that spoiled shit!
Dude, you had a little sip.
It wasn'’'t that big a deal.
No, no.
I said a silent "l'chaim"
and I drank the whole thing.
This is so embarrassing.
And I am dressed like an elf!
Alex! We have got to go!
Dude, you have
got to relax, man.
Seriously. Look.
My wife's in rehab,
my business has just
gone to shit...
Some dude kisses me.
At this point, really,
you want to know the truth?
Almost doesn't fucking faze me.
Oh.
Guys.
Can I talk to you guys?
Guys?
Are you dating Alex's dad?
No, I'm not.
It's okay if you are--
we like him and all-- but...
I'd have to tell Mom
you're dating a man.
Sure.
Sure. That's understandable.
But no, we're just friends.
But, you know, thank you
for being so open-minded.
I mean, honestly, I'm not sure
if I believe anything you say.
You lied to us.
You and Mom both lied.
You know what?
You're right. We did.
We shouldn't have.
We didn't want
you guys to worry.
But we should've been honest
with you guys.
I'm sorry.
So what's the truth?
Where is she?
Okay, well...
...your mom wasn't feeling
like herself, you know?
So she started to do some things
to make herself feel better.
Turns out those things
weren't good for her.
So, she decided,
'cause she's smart,
to go away to this place
where there are lots of doctors,
really good doctors,
to help her feel better
for real.
Is that what rehab is?
Yeah. Yeah, kind of.
Yeah, it's kind of like
when you're,
you know, when you get sick,
you guys go to the doctor,
you know?
Basically the same thing,
except...
it's just gonna take
a little longer.
Is she gonna die?
No, absolutely not.
She's gonna be fine.
She's gonna be better
than before, even.
Is that why she took
all those pills all the time?
Because she wasn't
feeling like herself?
Yeah. I didn't know
you knew that.
Well, I live with her.
It wasn't really a secret.
Yeah. I wish I was
as smart as you.
When is she coming home?
Well, it's gonna take
a little while, you know?
She's gonna be there
for a little while,
but then as soon as
she feels better,
she's gonna come
right back here to us,
to you guys.
Promise.
I know it's not the same,
but, you know...
I mean, I'm not going anywhere.
Okay? I'm right here
for you guys. -Mm.
- Okay?
- 'Kay. -'Kay.
Hey.
Perfect.
You want to see pictures...
...of where Mom is?
I don't think so.
Okay.
I'd like to.
Okay, check it out.
Look. Come here.
Pretty, right?
Mm-hmm.
So, third bid for the sign
was more than the first
and the second.
Ooh.
We can't do that right now.
That's just too expensive.
Maybe we'll get
one of those, uh,
you know, those flags that...
Forget that-- it's a dumb idea.
I don't even like those flags.
How about we just paint
the sign on the window?
That could look cool, right?
- Okay, yeah, we can do that.
- All right. Work on that.
- Okay. Will do.
- Okay. Okay.
Um, and, uh, these came for you.
Some letters that you sent
to Journeys rehab, I...
They've been returned.
Worth a shot.
I-I'm sorry, man.
No, we're all right.
It's all right.
Uh, what do you want
to talk to me about?
You said you wanted
to talk about something.
I did, um, but,
you know, I don't think
now's a great time--
No, no, no, it's a perfect time.
I got stuff to do later.
What do you got?
Okay, um...
Andy, you know how much
I love working for you.
Got another offer.
Actually, my buddy is opening
a gallery in Portland
and he wants me to manage it.
I-I just thought with all the...
all the changes going on
around here...
I'm really--
I'm really sorry.
Are you crazy?
You have to do that.
This is a great thing
for you, man.
- Yeah? Cool.
- Yeah.
I command you to do it.
You have to do it.
Seriously, man.
That's a great gig
for you, dude.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations, really.
Thank you, thank you.
Hey, Lola. Wow, you came.
You know what I was thinking?
I'm gonna send an archivist
over to your mom's studio
just to catalog everything.
Give the whole... whole thing
some academic grounding.
- You know?
- Hmm.
You know, make it available
to students.
- I like that.
- Yeah.
This piece...
it's really intense.
- My wife painted that.
- Mm.
Yeah, we're separated.
I mean--
I don't know why that matters.
Doesn't matter.
- That doesn't matter.
-Hey.
Hey. Hi. Sorry.
Um, Billie's on the phone.
I told her
that you're in a meeting,
but she said
that it's important.
Hold on a minute.
I-I got to get this.
- Yeah. Take your time.
- My daughter.
30 seconds.
Hey. What's up?
No, you can't see that.
Because it's PG-13, that's why.
Hold on. Sorry.
Don't even try that.
Put Tali on the phone.
Yeah.
I didn't say that.
I never said that.
Uh, 6:30.
I'm in the middle of something.
Turkey burgers, good idea.
Good call, I like it.
Yes, yes, yes. Go. Okay. Bye.
Hey. Sorry.
Oh, no, it's okay.
How old is your daughter?
Uh, twins, actually.
Uh, they're, uh, nine.
- Nine?
- Yeah.
Wow.
Moving into double digits,
though, real soon. Yeah.
- That is wonderful.
- Yeah.
- Great age.
- It is a really good age.
Yeah.
- Hi.
-Hey.
- Is he...?
- He's in a meeting.
Oh, hey, look who it is.
- Wow. Becca, can you...?
- Yep.
-Hi, Cy.
- Hello, sweetheart.
Aw, look at you.
You look great.
- Thank you. You, too.
- Well, thank you.
Yeah. -How you feeling?
How's it going with the...?
"With the...?"
- Good.
- Good!
Yeah, no, I'm good, I'm good.
Oh, great.
Great, great, great.
He looks busy, huh?
Yeah. Yes.
Yeah...
I think he forgot
about our hike.
- No, I don't think so.
- Yeah.
I don't think so, no.
Theresa Thompson's daughter
just popped in unexpectedly,
which I have to say
is very exciting.
This estate could be
the answer to our prayers.
It's been rough lately, so...
- Very...
- Oh.
I'm so excited about this hike
the two of you are going on.
Outdoors, fresh air.
I know he needs
his head cleared a little bit.
- Sure.
-So sorry.
I knew I had something.
Damn it.
Something.
Hey.
Lola Thompson,
this is my very pregnant--
and I think pretty mad at me--
daughter, Grace.
Grace, Lola.
- It's so nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
Uh, Dad, we can reschedule.
It's fine.
No. No, no, no.
I'm just gonna do this,
- and we'll go.
- When are you due?
Uh, six weeks.
It is the most magical time.
I'm actually pretty
uncomfortable.
Can I?
Yeah, of course.
My daughter's 17.
It all goes by
in the blink of an eye.
- Doesn't it?
-  Yeah.
Wait a minute, you--
I-I'm holding a breath work
at my house tomorrow night.
What are you guys doing?
Would you like to come?
Please come.
- Yeah.
-Yeah?
Yeah, I can-- I can learn
to breathe better.
Cy mentioned it
like I should know.
Dad, what's going on?
You're so secretive.
Well, things aren't
so hot right now.
The gallery,
we can't pay our rent, and...
Our artists aren't selling.
I don't know.
Hasn't been-- Hasn't been
my best year.
Are you thinking
you might close?
- No, no, no, no.
- Oh.
I'll figure it out.
Yeah, no, of course.
Of course you will.
Yeah.
The Therea estate will be, uh...
That'll be big if we get that.
That'll put us back on the map.
I don't know, it kills me.
I look around the office
and, man, I love
these people so much.
I hate seeing them out there.
If they have to go
look for a job, that'll kill me.
I'll tell ya.
Man, and I had everybody
back in the day.
I had such a good eye.
I don't know, maybe I lost it.
Maybe I'm out of touch.
Hold on.
You didn't lose anything.
And you're very in touch
for someone, mm...
- you know, matur-- mature.
- My age.
- Well, yeah.
- Yeah.
I get it. I get it.
Yeah.
The problem is, I am not even
remotely ready to be done yet.
I got so much more to give
and I've got great ideas
and things I want to do.
You know, I'm probably
in my head too much these days.
- You know how you do that?
- Yeah.
You get up there and... I got
a wife who won't talk to me.
I got a shitty business--
Can we sit for a second?
Oy.
This is hard, this hiking thing.
What? Don't look at--
Honey. We're not there yet.
I'm not looking.
There's no look.
There was a look.
I'm gonna be fine. Come on.
Everything's all right.
- Okay?
- Here.
If life isn't kicking your ass,
it's not doing its job.
I am so sorry I laid--
Oh, come on.
I shouldn't have laid
all of this on you. I'm sorry.
No, it's fine, honestly.
Honestly, this happens
all the time.
I just-- I can't control it.
It's fine. I promise.
Okay. -I just, I know
how much your work means to you.
And I don't know what to say.
I-I-I hate this, I...
I hate seeing you like this.
I hate being like this.
- What can I do?
- Nothing. I mean, we're fine.
Don't worry about it.
Just don't cry, 'cause if you
cry, then I'm gonna cry and...
we're up here in nature, crying.
I've never seen you cry.
- Really?
- Okay, once.
One time.
I hated it.
- Don't do it.
-  Okay.
Noted.
I'm gonna be fine.
Maybe I should cry.
Uh, well, if there was
a time to cry,
- this is-- this is a good time.
- Okay.
Things ain't that great,
but I won't.
- Not going to.
- Me, neither.
- I'm gonna be fine.
- Me, too.
I promise you. Look at me.
We're gonna be good, right?
Don't worry about me.
I'm gonna be fine.
I'm always fine.
Come on, let's go.
Let's go climb a...
hill or something.
Come on. Oldie and preggers.
Dad.
Oh, sorry, sorry.
GRACE [grunts]:
Okay.
What year did
the California gold rush begin?
What year was it?
Was it... 1848?
Thank you very much.
Nice! Nice!
And where was it
first discovered?
That's easy.
-Really?
- Yeah.
Is it...
...uh, Sutter's Mill?
Mose Goodrich,
ladies and gentlemen.
Thank you very much.
There you go.
How's everybody feeling
about our dual sleepovers?
- Excited.
- Very excited. -Me, too.
But what are you ever
going to do without us?
Me? Huge party.
Big, big party here.
Yeah, catered.
-Really?
- People, celebrities.
- Dad.
- DJ.
- What are you really doing?
- No.
Billie and I have a thing.
I'm Billie.
I mean Gracie.
Sorry. Sorry, sorry.
There, that's you.
That's yours.
Let's get going.
That lady at the front desk
freaks me out.
She kind of scares me, really.
Did you pack me
a chocolate chip cookie?
- I did.
- The kind I like?
Exactly. Crispy on the outside.
Nice and gooey and soft
in the center.
- Did I get one, too?
- Yes, you did.
You got two.
-Hey! I heard that.
- Hey, come on, come on.
Come on, come on.
Deep breathing brings you
to a higher vibration.
Take it nice and slow.
Tune in to what's happening
inside your body.
Feel your stress reducing,
your anxiety melting.
In the areas around your chest,
your shoulders.
Tune in to it.
Tuned. I'm tuned right there.
Breathe in through your nose,
out through your mouth.
Let your body move organically.
Now let's bring some movement,
involving your shoulders.
Your arms.
Now, chin to chest, and hold.
Open with breath.
Yeah. Come on, guys.
Get out all of
that negative energy.
Really get it out of you.
All of that trauma,
it all lives in your body.
Shake it out.
I'm shaking.
And let go.
Now you let the light in.
- Through your toes.
- Okay.
Into your kneecaps,
your mind,
your heart.
♪ Sanando, Sanando ♪
♪ Sanando, Sanando... ♪
Now, take it up a notch.
Come on.
That's it.
♪ Sanando... ♪
♪ Sanando, Sanando ♪
♪ Sanando ♪
♪ See ♪
♪ We're dancing ♪
♪ On the rim of the world ♪
♪ We're dancing
on the rim of the world ♪
♪ We're dancing ♪
♪ Sanando, Sanando... ♪
I want you to channel a word
that describes
what you feel you need most
from the world right now.
We're all going to shout
our words at the exact same time
- and release them.
- Help!
I was... gonna count to three.
Sorry.
How you feeling, Goodrich?
- Fantastic.
- Yeah?
I didn't-- I didn't know
that I needed this.
Turns out, man,
I really needed this. -
Honestly, th-thanks
for inviting us.
This was really, uh,
this was something.
- Yeah. That makes me so happy.
- Oh, good.
Yeah, I wanted to talk to you.
I-I've been thinking
about this a lot.
Um...
I like the idea of being
with a boutique gallery
that really understands
and gives us the attention
that we deserve.
You know? And-and more
than that, more importantly,
I'm all about family, and...
watching you tonight
with your daughter, I-I...
It really spoke to me
the kind of man that you are.
And, uh, I think
that's the kind of man,
kind of person,
that I want out in the world
representing my mom.
Oh, man. Wow. That's great.
Thanks. One night in Topanga,
all of a sudden I'm a hugger.
This-- Oh, wow, I can't
tell you, I am thrilled.
- Just thrilled.
- Yeah, I am, too.
I promise you,
we're gonna do great for you.
I know you will.
ANDY [exhales]:
I'm breathing right.
I'm back in business.
- This-- that was fun.
-Yeah.
And it's all because
of you, you know that, right?
Yeah, hardly, but I'll take it.
No, it was.
It was fun. Thanks, hon.
Let's go do something.
Let's celebrate. Come on.
Oy, it's late.
Plus, what about your kids?
- Don't you have to go home?
- Eh, they're at sleepovers.
Come on, what do you want to do?
- You can't drink.
-  No.
Okay, let's go
get some ice cream.
You love mint chip.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Okay. I know a cute
little place in Venice.
If we hurry, we can get there
before it closes.
Let's go.
Hold on a minute.
Let me just do this.
Yello. Hello.
Hey, hi.
Calm down.
Do you have a temperature?
Yeah.
Okay, okay, okay.
I'll come there.
I'll be there in 30 minutes.
30 minutes is not a long time.
Do you want to stay
on the phone with me?
It's gonna be okay.
I love you, too, honey.
It's Grace.
I'm Grace.
It's Billie. Sorry. Billie.
She's not feeling well. Can...
Can we have a rain check
on that ice cream cone?
Yeah.
Okay.
Hey, Ann.
Andy. Hey.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- Geez, I must be early.
Grace didn't tell me
you were gonna be here.
Well, me and the kids
baked some cookies,
and we just dropped them off.
How are you?
I'm, uh, you know...
No, I-I'm sorry.
Grace told me. I...
I feel for Naomi.
Yeah, okay. Thank you.
Thanks. Yeah.
Hey, congratulations.
You're big-time now.
That-that's a great gig.
- Way to go.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, thanks. Uh...
I'm crazy busy.
I travel nonstop,
which I don't love
so much anymore,
but I'll slow down
once the baby comes.
Yeah, sure, sure.
- Yeah.
Anyway, how are you holding up?
You didn't answer.
Uh, you know, okay,
uh, surprisingly.
I'm-I'm okay.
You're always okay.
Well...
That was a compliment.
Didn't feel like it,
but, you know, it's okay.
Wait, you got
the Theresa Thompson estate.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Oh, wow.
- That's major. Yeah, yeah.
- Yeah, it's good.
It's good. Yeah, yeah.
You know, I think
I turned you on to her.
Oh, I don't think so.
Why aren't you at the gallery?
It's almost 11:00.
This has got to be a first.
I don't know, you know,
go to the market,
uh, drop the kids off
at school, come here.
You at the market?
Me at the market.
I'm a market guy now.
Hey, if you're early,
you want to go get
a cup of coffee or something?
Take a walk?
Come on, just say yes
before, you know,
before you think of an excuse.
Oh, wow. Yeah.
- Oh, wow. Just so stunning.
-She still has it.
Have you thought about, um...
Hey, let me ask you a question.
What do you think about Pete?
- Oh, Pete's great.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- No, I-I like Pete.
It's just that she's so funny
and Pete is, like, so not.
Uh, he's nice, you know.
Yeah, but yeah, who cares?
- He's gonna be a great dad.
- Yeah, you're probably right.
She's the great one.
Oh, my God, she's fantastic.
You say that
like you just met her.
No, I mean, we've been spending
a lot of time together.
That's...
You did a great job, Ann.
Really.
You were always willing to,
you know,
give anything up for the family.
Thanks. I admire that. Really.
You see, that's the difference
between me and you.
I never saw it as
giving anything up.
Ann. There you are.
Oh.
Um, Andy, this is Barry Klein.
Nice to finally meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
-Oh, that's right.
We're taking Grace out to lunch,
if you want to join us.
You know, I would,
but I got to go to the gallery,
and then I got a--
I got a thing I got to do.
But I'm gonna see you
at Christmas anyway
at Gracie's, right?
Actually, um, we're going
to New York for the holidays.
You know, quick trip
before the baby comes.
Can't beat Christmas
in the city, eh?
No, you can't.
It's gonna be beautiful.
It's gonna be great.
Thanks. Shall we?
Uh, yeah.
Take care, Andy.
Hey, that's pretty good, guys.
Lola Thompson's here.
Oh, already?
Okay.
Definitely not Swiss Mocha,
I can tell you that.
Okay.
Whites will make you crazy.
Simply White.
- Simply White. Okay.
- That's the color.
- Hey, hi.
- Hey.
You're early.
That's okay, that's okay.
That's a good thing.
PR team's not here yet,
and I have got a ton of stuff
to go over with you.
First, come meet my kids.
Yeah, Andy, wait. Wait.
Um, I came early
'cause I need to talk to you.
Okay.
Yeah, there's really
no easy way to say this.
Um, it's not personal, okay?
-  Okay.
- I want you to know that.
Oh, I should just
say it, I guess.
Um, I gave the estate
to another gallery.
One in New York.
They flew out here,
and they, uh,
they-they lined me up
with a huge buyer already,
promised me a-a show
in every city.
New York, London, Paris.
We... we even got accepted
to Basel.
Yeah. Wait a minute.
Is this a done deal?
Yeah, it is.
I just signed
the contracts, and...
you know,
we didn't have any, so...
No, we didn't.
We didn't have a contract
'cause all we had was,
you know, your word.
Andy.
Let me ask you something.
The whole thing about, you know,
family and everything,
what was that? Was that--
That was true, of course.
This wasn't an easy move for me.
I-I wasn't looking for this.
They pursued me.
The offer was just...
It's a lot of money, Andy.
I'm a 50-year-old single mom.
- I know, I know--
-Dad, help!
It's Alex!
Excuse me.
Hi. I'm looking for
Alexander Koch.
He was brought in about
an hour ago. I'm his father.
Okay, uh, room 702,
down the hall, to the right.
Okay, thank you.
Hey.
I was shooting
all the way in Burbank.
Here's the deal.
The seizure, mild.
- It was the fall, okay?
- Yeah, yeah.
Okay, okay, here's the plan.
They're gonna
keep him overnight,
just to make sure he doesn't
have another episode, right?
- Yeah.
- And as soon as he's okay,
they're just gonna send him
home in the morning,
and everything will be okay.
He was so great, man.
He was so brave
getting his stitches.
He must have been so scared.
I can't believe I wasn't there.
Oh, come on,
don't beat yourself up.
He's gonna be fine.
Honestly, don't worry about it.
I'm sorry I took my eye off him.
No. God, come on.
Hey, you got a gig, huh?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
A guest spot on a soap.
- That's good.
- Yeah.
- How'd it go?
- Eh, all right.
- All right, good.
- I finished it.
You want some tea
or something? Coffee?
- No. No, no, no, no.
- You sure?
No, you should go.
It's late. You should--
No, no, no,
I'll stay here with you.
- No, no. Thank you. I'm fine.
- Okay.
Okay, okay.
All right.
Hey, don't worry,
he's gonna be fine.
Don't worry.
You look worried. Come here.
- There.
- Thank you.
All right. Take it easy, buddy.
Oh, yeah, nope.
All right, sorry.
- Hey.
- How you doing, man?
Thanks for coming.
- Wouldn't miss this.
- Thank you very much.
- Onward.
- Thanks, buddy.
- Hey, Doc.
- Hey, love you, man.
Thanks, man.
- Ed, you came.
- I can't believe it.
I just can't believe
Goodrich is closing.
Hey.
Well, here we are.
- Yeah, here we are.
- How you feeling, boss?
Like I'm having
an out-of-body experience.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah.
Who invited the accountant?
Jesus, look at him.
Yeah, hi.
Hey.
I'm gonna go up
and say a few words.
Yeah, okay. Listen.
I love you, pal.
Love you, too, buddy.
Hey.
I couldn't have done this
without you, you know.
I want you to know that.
Hi. Hey.
First off...
I just want to thank everyone
for even coming tonight.
This is, uh,
this is a special night.
A sad one, but, you know,
monumental for me.
This is big.
You know,
the Buddhists say, in the end,
there are really only
three things that matter:
how much you've loved,
how gently you've lived
and how gracefully
you let go of the things
that really weren't
even meant for you.
I haven't lived that gently.
And, uh, I think you all know
I have a little hard time
letting go of things.
But then there's love.
Yeah. Man.
And the love, I mean,
I feel so much love
here tonight.
And I have to tell you,
I have loved this gallery,
boy, with everything I've got.
You know, when you see
something with your eyes,
like, you know,
schoolchildren, let's say,
crossing the street
in maybe a little bit
of falling rain
or the way that morning sun,
you know, comes
right through your window
and hits a bowl of fruit
on your kitchen counter...
Or, even better...
...that smile
on your daughter's face.
You know, you...
you close your eyes
and you think,
"I have to remember this."
Because, in that moment,
that's a piece of art.
That's just art.
Oh, boy. Okay.
Well, this has been
a long journey, folks.
But it's been
the ride of my life.
Hey, thanks for coming.
They all come at the end.
Dad.
Eh, it's true.
Hey, it was so nice
to see everybody.
Honestly, it was great, but,
really, did kind of feel like
a guest at my own funeral,
you know?
Well, if you ask me,
I think this is actually
a really good thing.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, like a whole new chapter.
Yeah, maybe.
Hey, I'm gonna get
to see the kids a lot more,
travel a little bit.
Maybe even take
some tango lessons.
And you're gonna be
a grandfather.
Oh, come on, Goodrich,
it's just a word.
Okay, I got to--
I got to sit down.
No, no,
don't worry about it, Dad.
I got it.
- Honey...
- No need to help me.
Honey, you don't have to nail me
at every given opportunity.
Nicely done, thank you.
Oh.
- Grandfather.
- Yeah.
Grandfather's like a guy
with bushy eyebrows
and a walking stick
and a tweed jacket.
I feel like you're describing
the old man from Up.
Look, I know this conversation
is gonna be held against me
at some point,
so can we just kind of,
you know, delete it
from the transcript
and let it be known
that I am really, really
excited about the baby.
In fact, the word "ecstatic"
comes to mind.
Here.
I don't know if you've noticed,
but I am extremely pregnant.
Ah, you're fine.
You're-you're fully baked.
You're good. Trust me,
I've been through
enough pregnancies.
I know.
Drink with me.
Speaking of being
an expert in this field,
um, I have
my last doctor's appointment
before Christmas tomorrow,
and it's getting
a little uncomfortable to drive.
Mom's in New York
and Pete has to work, so...
- Now...
- I was wondering if you...
Your old man is
very, very, very available.
He would take you.
Gladly.
Kidding me? Can't wait.
Thanks for
coming tonight, honey.
I know, but still,
- it was nice.
- Come on.
You know,
this kind of feels like
an end of an era for me, too.
Hmm.
Well, this midlife crisis
is no walk in the park,
I'll tell you that.
I didn't realize you were
planning to live till 120.
Please don't, okay?
I don't think I can afford
the therapy bills.
Ooh, that was nice. 120.
Oh, my God.
Hallelujah.
♪ Jingle bells, jingle bells,
listen to them ring ♪
♪ Bringing all the happiest
wishes they can bring ♪
♪ Oh, jingle bells,
jingle bells ♪
♪ Let's have a ball ♪
♪ Happy New Year, everyone ♪
♪ Merry Christmas, all. ♪
Merry Christmas.
You're home.
Yeah, I'm-- I'm done.
I'm out, so...
God, it's so quiet in here.
Where are the kids?
They're at their friend's,
some... Alex's house.
Oh.
Yeah, I-I know his dad
a little bit.
I can't wait to see them.
Look, I'm so sorry.
I-I should've called.
I just, um...
I didn't...
I didn't really know
if you would want to see me.
No, I mean, I knew
the 90 days were up
'cause I got this
little reminder on my phone...
...that went off, so...
of course I want to see you.
Andy--
Why did you have to do it
like that?
I would've helped you.
I didn't know what else to do.
You know, I was scared.
I was so scared.
And I didn't abandon our family.
I-I really hope
that you know that.
I know. I know.
I just did not want them
to see me like that.
I know. -It's not how
I want them to think of me.
I know. I know.
- I know that.
- Okay.
I'm sorry, Naomi.
It's, like, the simplest thing
to say, but...
this is the...
first time I've had
a chance to say it
while actually looking at you.
Thank you.
Anyway, um,
I'm on the other side now.
And-and I'm--
And I'm doing good.
You know, recovery,
it's just such a journey,
but I'm-I'm starting to feel
more like myself.
Great. Good, good, good.
Hey, I really want to help you
this time, okay?
'Cause I've been doing a lot
of reading about it and, uh...
I just really want
to help you, okay?
I love you.
I've been--
I've been doing, um,
a lot of thinking.
I've had a lot of time to think,
and we are gonna...
be better as friends.
Oh. Okay.
Deep down, didn't you
kind of always know that...
we weren't gonna make it?
Uh...
Actually, I can't say
that I did, no.
Didn't see that one.
We've got a lot to be
grateful for. -Yeah.
You know, we got
two beautiful kids and...
you're gonna be a grandfather.
Yep.
Yeah, about...
Oh, shit.
Come on, come on, come on.
GRACE [recorded]:
Hi. You've reached Grace--
Ah, geez.
If you leave a message,
I'll call you back.
Shit.
Hi. You've reached Grace.
Gracie, honey, I'm on my way.
Okay? Okay, okay.
Ah, fuck.
GRACE [recorded]:
Hi. You've reached Grace.
If you leave a message,
I'll call you back.
Honey, I'm on my way, okay?
I'll be there in a few minutes.
Right there is fine. Thank you.
- Oh, my God.
- I'm here.
You remembered
you were supposed to pick me up?
No, I know, honey.
I called Pete,
and he said to meet you here.
I tried to reach you.
What happened, huh?
Something come up with the kids?
Did you forget?
What was it, Dad?
Uh, well, uh, Naomi showed up.
Oh. Okay, well, I'm glad
that she's up and running.
Maybe now I can just go back
to being someone
you call from the car.
Or when you need to know what
temperature to bake a potato.
- Oh, Gracie, come on.
- Are we done here?
Because I'm late for a doctor's
appointment because of you.
I'm sorry. Look, the woman
just showed up at my house.
What was I supposed to do?
I haven't talked to her
in 90 days.
- I have to talk to her.
- No, I get it, I get it.
- Priorities. I get it.
- No, honey, come on.
Look, I'm only
a few minutes late. -
I'm here now.
Let's just go upstairs.
- You don't get it, do you?
- Get what?
I waited for you like an idiot.
I'm so sorry. I feel awful.
I hate letting you down.
You hate letting me down?
Yes, I do.
You've let me down
my whole life.
This-- This is nothing.
This is a doctor's appointment.
How have I let you...?
Don't answer that.
Let's go upstairs.
I thought you changed.
I really did.
I thought you'd grown up.
And-and you know what?
Maybe you have.
But it's all for them.
I'm not a part of that.
I'm a part of the original cast.
I don't get to reap the benefits
of the new and improved
Andy Goodrich
who makes you pancakes
and shows you old movies.
No, no, I got
the never available, never home,
never asked you
how your day was Goodrich.
Honey, this is really
not good for you right now.
Oh, really?
'Cause I think it is.
I-I think it's really good
to get things off your chest
that you've held in
for 30 years.
I'm mad at you.
And I have been
for as long as I can remember.
Just a-a steady stream of mad
with spurts of liking you
in between.
Do you know how hard it is
for me to watch you
be father of the year
all of a sudden?
Do you know how painful
it is for me?
They get a version of you
that I never had.
I-I never even got to live
with you past the age of 11.
I don't even remember
what you look like in pajamas.
We're just friends, you and I,
but-but they have you,
all of you.
Th-They get you,
and I never did.
But do you know
who shows up for you?
Do you know who's
always there for you? Me.
- I know.
- For better or for worse, man.
Because I'm the only person
that loves you
as much as you love yourself.
And another thing.
D-Do you know why
I married Pete?
Because he's nothing like you.
And maybe that, maybe that's
why you don't like him.
Okay, honey, please.
Do you know that every time
I-I see you,
I want to run into your arms
and slap you?
I mean, it's the single most
confusing thing in my life.
Because nobody, nobody can
break my heart like--
Oh, my God.
What? What's going on?
Oh, my God, it's happening
and I'm with you!
What? What's happening?
- I'm sorr-- What?
- It, Dad! It!
- Are you sure?
- Yes, I'm sure.
- Okay. This is okay.
- The doctor last week told me
that I was on track
for full term,
but I'm not due
for three and a half more weeks.
- Okay. Okay.
- And-and I'm not dilated.
And this isn't supposed
to happen
- with your first baby.
- Right.
Oh, my God, Mom is
in New York and Pete--
- No, we're good.
- Pete. Okay.
- What do we do?
- Y-You got to call Pete.
You got to call Pete
and you got to tell him
he's got to grab the bag.
Got it, got it.
Should we go upstairs?
No, Dad, we have to go
to the hospital!
Got it. Let's go. Okay.
W-Will you call Pete?
Where's your car?
Come on. Come on. Here. Hey.
Pete. Pete, Grace is in labor.
We're on our way
to the hospital.
Let's go. Come on.
It's go time.
Tell him to grab the bag.
Hey, grab the bag, dude.
And the slippers by my bedside.
Okay, and grab the slippers,
her slippers,
on her side of the bed.
Yeah, and, uh, and my cozy robe,
not the one that I blow-dry
my hair in, the other one.
Grab the cozy robe,
not the other one,
not the hair-drying one.
What else?
- Aromatherapy spray.
- Aromatherapy.
Don't forget
the aromatherapy spray.
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
And the cord blood kit.
- It's over by the front door.
- Do you want to talk to him?
Okay.
Okay, sweetie.
- You're having a contraction.
- Squeeze my hand.
Just, there you go.
Squeeze that.
There you go.
You're doing great.
It's almost over.
- Worst is over.
- Dad?
- Yeah?
- I'm really glad you're here.
Me, too, babe.
Me, too. I'm so glad.
I'm really sorr--
- Squeeze this one for a while.
- I'm okay now, Dad.
I'm okay, I'm okay.
I'm okay right now.
- Okay. Come on.
- Yeah, I'm okay.
Oh, and I'm sorry about
all the horrible things
that I said to you.
Please, don't even
think about that.
Don't worry about that.
You're hormonal.
No, no, I meant them.
I just shouldn't have said them.
It was really mean of me,
and I hate when I get like that,
and I'm really sorry.
Don't worry about it.
It's okay.
-  Okay.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
- Hey.
- Yeah?
You're having a baby tonight.
- Yeah.
- In fact,
this baby might be born
on Christmas.
It's the most
religious thing I've ever done.
Well, Grace,
you're progressing really fast.
So, if you're comfortable
with the epidural,
I think we should
move ahead with it.
Okay, I-I actually
was kind of hoping
to go without that,
if that's okay.
It could slow things down
but will definitely help
with the pain.
Yeah. Okay. She wants that.
Okay, looks like I'm gonna
be here for a little while,
but I'll call you as soon as
the baby's born, okay?
Yes, I promise.
I promise.
I know.
I'm glad she's home, too.
Okay. Okay, love you.
Okay, love you. Hey, Pete.
Oh, God.
- Come on, Pete.
- Hey.
- Whoa. You all right?
- How is she?
- She's good.
- Oh, good.
Come on. Come here.
- Hey.
- You okay?
- How is she doing?
- Oh, she's doing great.
I think the feeling's starting
to come back in my hand.
- I'm gonna be a dad.
- You're gonna be a dad.
Good luck with that, Pete.
Uh-oh.
Hey, Grace?
We are gonna go ahead
and turn you on your side, okay?
-Wait, what? Pete!
- Wh-What-What's happening?
- I don't know what's happening.
-Hello, everybody.
Okay, let's see what's going on.
Oh, okay, so your contractions
are just one on top of the other
and the baby's having
a hard time
normalizing its heart rate.
So, let's put her on
her other side. Here we go.
- So, Mom and Dad.
- GRACE and PETE: Yeah.
This is the plan.
I'm gonna just wait
for a couple of minutes,
see if the heart rate
normalizes by itself.
We want to see
the heart rate go up.
And if not, I'm gonna go in and
perform an emergency C-section.
Wait, what?
Oh, my God.
Hey, let's just
talk through this, okay?
- Hey.
- Yeah.
- Let's just talk through this.
- Okay.
Okay? The baby's gonna be
just fine, I promise.
Hold my hand. Hey.
We're gonna bring the baby home
to that beautiful
gender-neutral nursery
you set up.
And we're not gonna sleep
for like six months,
but it won't matter.
And then, before you know it,
it's gonna be
the first day of school.
Can you believe that?
But I'm gonna be a basket case.
But you, you're gonna be solid
and put together.
A total ace.
And then you're gonna
break down in the car.
-And we're gonna
have great family vacations.
Because you make
the best itineraries.
Yeah. And we're gonna
take a picture of us
holding the Leaning Tower
of Pisa like that.
And we're also gonna make
a ton of mistakes.
But then we're gonna
have a second kid...
Oh.
And we're gonna make less.
I think our baby's gonna be
really embarrassed by us
for a while in high school.
Especially me. I know it.
But we'll get through it.
And we're gonna have each other.
- Right?
- Yeah.
And then college.
We're buying sheets
for an extra-long twin?
How did that happen?
I think our baby's
really gonna miss us
when they go to college.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah.
And I think
we're gonna get ourselves
a little apartment
on the East Coast.
Have ourselves
a little renaissance.
It's gonna be so great, Grace.
And it's just starting.
Right here, right now.
Yeah.
- I love you so much.
- I love you.
Dad, are you crying?
No.
No, not at all.
Okay, baby's heart rate
is coming back up.
- Good job, Dad.
- Oh, wow.
-Take a quick look.
-You sure?
-  Yeah.
- Okay, great.
Let me take a look.
Okay. I think
we're ready to push.
You ready, Grace?
- I-I--
-You got this.
- I'm ready.
- Yes, you are.
- Okay.
- You got it.
All right,
she's ten centimeters.
- Pushing. I'm gonna--
- Everyone, step out
- who's not essential, please.
- I'm gonna step out of here.
- Okay.
-Okay. Just relax.
Hey, sweetie.
Yeah, Dad?
One more thing, you know,
before I go.
You know you're
my soulmate, right?
Just wanted to tell you.
That's it.
Okay, I'll...
- Okay, let's do it.
-Okay.
- Let's go.
-Let's do this.
♪ Have yourself ♪
♪ A merry little Christmas ♪
♪ Let your heart be light ♪
♪ Next year ♪
♪ All our troubles ♪
♪ Will be out of sight... ♪
Grace did beautifully.
- Okay. Good.
- She rested. Baby's healthy
and, I don't always say this,
but adorable.
Thanks. That's great. Man.
Thanks very much. Boy...
Phew. That was scary.
You were great.
You were really great.
Man, I didn't think that...
I'd get this emotional.
Thank you.
Oh, please, well,
don't apologize,
- and you are welcome.
- Thanks.
Wait a minute. I almost forgot.
It's a girl.
♪ Faithful friends
who are dear to us ♪
♪ Will be near to us ♪
♪ Once more... ♪
Knock, knock.
It's a girl.
How about that?
She was amazing,
a superhero, really.
Oh, I'm not surprised.
Of course, she is a superhero.
- How you feeling, honey?
- Oh, man, I am exhausted.
Oh, you meant Grace.
- Yeah.
I'm happy.
- Yeah, I'll bet.
- Yeah.
You know, babies are not
supposed to be this gorgeous.
She's beautiful.
- Right?
- Yeah.
Oh, so cute.
- Pedro.
-  Hey.
Way to go, buddy.
You did good. You did great.
You're a good dad.
Can we come in?
- Oh, yeah, come in, come in.
- Yeah, come here.
Come on, come on. Come on.
- Aunt and Uncle are here.
- Merry Christmas.
She's so cute.
Aw.
Oh, I love her little nose.
That's so cute.
Yeah. Me, too.
Dad?
You want to hold the baby?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Here.
Of course.
- You remember how?
- I do.
Okay.
Like riding a bike.
Hold your little head up.
♪ True love will find you
in the end ♪
That smell.
♪ You'll find out just who... ♪
I'm your granddad.
Welcome.
♪ Don't be sad ♪
♪ I know you will ♪
♪ And don't give up until ♪
♪ True love will find you
in the end ♪
♪ This is a promise
with a catch ♪
♪ Only if you're looking
can it find you ♪
♪ 'Cause true love
is searching, too ♪
♪ But how can it recognize you ♪
♪ Unless you step out
into the light ♪
♪ Don't be sad,
I know you will ♪
♪ And don't give up until ♪
♪ True love will find you
in the end. ♪